Guide to the Robert Trent Jones papers, ca. 1924-2003.
Jones, Robert Trent papers
- Series III. Project Records
  - Project files
    - Sands Point Golf Club, Port Washington, NY, 1961-1963 (Box 230, Folder 21)
    - Sands Point Golf Club, Port Washington, NY, 1984 (Box 230, Folder 22)
    - Shinnecock Hills Golf Club, Southampton, NY, 1969-1974 (Box 230, Folder 23)
    - Stanford University, Stanford, CA, 1965-1968 (Box 230, Folder 24)
    - Two Bridges Country Club, Lincoln Park, NJ, 1969 (Box 230, Folder 25)
    - United States Land, Inc., Palo Alto, CA, 1968-1970 (Box 230, Folder 26)
  - Files and Technical Specifications
    - Seabright Gulf and Country Club, Ocean Pines, MD - Specs, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Bristol Harbor Village - Specs (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Carolina Trace, Sanford, NC - Specs (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Oglebay Park, Wheelin, WV - Specs, c.1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Oakland Hills Country Club, Birmingham, MI - Specs, c.1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Biscayne Village Golf Club, Ft. Lauderdale, FL - Specs, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Country Club of Paducah, Paducah, KY - Specs, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Country Club of Paducah, Paducah, KY - Specs Superseded (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Ransom Oaks Country Club, Amherst, NY - Specs (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - North Hills Country Club, Little Rock, AK - Specs, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Cerromar Golf Course (Formerly 'Brenas'), Dorado Beach, Puerto Rico - Specs, 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Canoe Brook Country Club (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Palmetto Dunes Resort, Hilton Head Island, NC - Specs, c.1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Alabama International Country Club, Talladega County, AL - Specs (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Skyway Golf Course, Myrtle Beach, SC - Specs, c.1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Cacapon State Park, WV - Specs, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Cinnamon Hill Golf Course, Montego Bay, Jamaica - Specs, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Arcadian Shores, Myrtle Beach, SC - Specs (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Celebrity Country Club - Irrigation System Specs, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Crag Burn Golf Course, Elma, NY, c.1970 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - The Ranch of the Pedernals, Johnson City, TX - Specs (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Andalucia La Nueva Golf Course, Marbella, Malaga, Spain - Specs, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Golf Saint Francis, Guadeloupe - Specs, c.1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Seabrook Island, SC 2nd 18 - Specs, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Shawnee Inn Golf Course - Irrigation Specs, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Augusta, GA - Masters Golf Tournament, 1965-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Augusta National Golf Club, Augusta, GA, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Augusta National Golf Club, Augusta, GA, 1934-1949 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Baltusrol Golf Club, Springfield, NJ - 67th Open (inactive), 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Birmingham, Country Club of, Birmingham, AL, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bloomfield Hills Golf Course, Bloomfield Hills, MI, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Bloomfield Hills Golf Course, Bloomfield Hills, MI, 1964-1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Brasilia Golf Course, Brasilia, Brazil - Gates Pan American, 1964-1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Bristol Harbor Golf Club, Canandaigua, NY, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Bristol Harbor Golf Club, Canandaigua, NY - Publicity, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Bristol Harbor Golf Club, Canandaigua, NY, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain - Publicity, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain - CBR Active Job, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain - Valderrama Golf Course, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain - Valderrama Golf Course, New Course, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain - McMicking, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain - Club de Golf de Con Chudo - Specs and Plans, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain - Specs and Plans, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain - McMicking, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain - McMicking, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Snead, Sam - Scottsdale, AZ, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Snead, Sam - St. Petersburg, FL, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf -Director's Meeting Minutes, 1961-1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf -General Correspondence (4), 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Snead, Sam - Greenbrier, WY, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf - Lighting, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf - Titusville, FL, 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf - San Diego, CA, 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf -General Correspondence (1), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf -General Correspondence (2), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf -General Correspondence (3), 1958-1960 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf - Colton, CA, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf - Alviso, CA, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf - Fresno, CA, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf - Rialto, CA, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf - Sacramento, CA, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf - Orlando, FL, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Snead, Sam - All American Golf - Texas, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Marrakech project files, 1990-1993 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - La Palmier specs, sketches (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
    - Miscellaneous maps (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified aerial (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Typical specifications manual, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Job categorisation (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Colgate, S Bayard, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Puerto Rico, Rockefeller, 1954-1960 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - IBM Poughkeepsie, 1942-1943 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - The Voyage of Columbus map (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Baiting Hollow Country Club, Riverhead Long Island, NY - Specs, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Belmeadow Country Club, Clarksburg, WV - Specs, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Black Hall Golf Club, Old Lyme, CT - Specs, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Bristol Harbor Golf Course Pump Station, Canandaigua, NY - Specs, c.1970-1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Broadmoor Golf Club, Colorado Springs, CO, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Country Club on North Carolina - 4th Nine Addition - Specs (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Deal Golf and Country Club - Irrigation Specs (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Dorado Project 85, Puerto Rico, c.1965-1966 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Fairview Country Club, Greenwich, CT - Specs (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Ferncroft Country Club, Topsfield, MA - New Nine Specs, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Firestone Country Club, Akron, OH - Specs, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Fort Gordon Golf Course, Augusta, GA - Specs, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Fuengirola, Malaga, Spain - Irrigation System Specs (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Geneva, Country Club of, Geneva, Switzerland - Irrigation System Specs, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Golden Triangle Golf Course, Anne Arundel County, MD - Specs, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Great Swamp, Chatham, NJ - Irrigation System Specs (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Green Lakes State Park Golf Course - Specs (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - International Golf Club, Bolton, MA - Specs (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Inverrary Golf and Country Club, Ft. Lauderdale, FL - Specs (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Kings Point West Golf Club, Sun City Center, FL - Specs, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Kings Point, Delray Beach, FL - Irrigation Specs (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Land of the Fifth Season, St. Louis, MO - Specs (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Moor Algerton, Leeds, UK - Specs (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Montauk Golf Links, Montauk, NY - Specs, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - National Golf Links of America, South Hampton, NY - Irrigation System Specs (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Sleepy Hollow, Scarborough, NY - Specs, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Sodem, Fort de France, Martinique - Specs, c.1973 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Spring Green, Spring Green, WI - Specs, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Sugar Creek Country Club, Houston, TX - Original Irrigation System Specs (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Sugar Creek Country Club, Houston, TX - Continuous 18-Hole Specs (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Tanglewood Golf Course, Clemmons, NC - First 18 Specs, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Tanglewood Golf Course, Clemmons, NC - Specs, 1969-1972 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Three Island Country Club, Broward County, FL - Specs (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Topsfield Inn and Country Club, Danvers, MA - Specs, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Valderrama Golf Club, Sotogrande, Spain - Specs, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Valley Brook Country Club (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - York, Philip and Celtic Manor correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Celtic Manor maps, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Celtic Manor miscellany, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Golf de Joyenval billings and payments (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Golf de Joyenval plans (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Marbella Golf y Club de Campo billings and payments, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Marbella Golf y Club de Campo contract for shaping/grassing tees, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Marbella Golf y Club de Campo drafts, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Marbella Golf y Club de Campo correspondence, memos, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Marbella Golf y Club de Campo Payables, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Marbella Golf y Club de Campo design contracts, 1990s (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Costa Smerelda (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Elmendorf Air Force Base (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Lysander Community Golf Course, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Greenville Country Club (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Irrigation Pumping System, Alberta Parks, Kananaskis (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Ridgewood, River Bend, Rockleigh, Stone Mountain (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Tam O'Shanter, U. of Georgia (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Playa Dorada, Spanish (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Lysander drainage (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Playa Dorada, English, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Port Royal (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Muttontown, Offutt, Panther Valley (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Playa Grande, Spanish (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Lysander grounds (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Rayburn Country Club technical specifications (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - The Rail, Sherman, Illinois specifications and conditions (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Pilgrim's Harbor Country Club contracts, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - River Shores Golf Course specifications (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Crumpin-Fox Club information, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Adare Manor, Ireland, 1990-1995 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Ballybunion Golf Club correspondence, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Celtic Manor contracts and documents, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Vidauban expense reports, 1981-1989 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Tucker, Anthony and RL Day, Inc. expense reports, 1986-1988 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Playa Grande report, 1994-1995 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Coral Ridge Country Club surveys (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Carlisle and LeCates invoices, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Playa Dorada, Dominican Republic. Cancun, 1970s (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Punta Cana executed design agreement, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Punta Cana correspondence and memos, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Punta Cana contracts, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Punta Cana expenses, 1988-1989 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Punta Cana yacht club, 1987-1991 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Monsignor Della Casa design billings, payments, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Monsignor Della Casa correspondence, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Monsignor Della Casa drafts (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Monsignor Della Casa executed agreement, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Madeira contracts, billings, payments, 1990-1991 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Madeira drafts (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Madeira correspondence and memos, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Marrakesh, Abdelai Berrada, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Marrakesh correspondence and memos, 1990-1991 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Marrakesh contract with golf course architect, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Marrakesh billings and payments, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - CYD Japan golf course agreement, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - CYD Japan drafts, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - CYD Japan correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - CYD Japan billings and payments, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - CYD Japan agreement between Jones and Howell, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Ipswich club folder and packet (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Ipswich correspondence, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Arcola Country Club payment, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Bellerive Country Club billings and payments, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Bellerive design agreement, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - Bellerive miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Crumpin-Fox Club correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 84, Folder 29)
    - Crumpin-Fox Club payments, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - Crumpin-Fox design agreement, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - Crumpin-Fox construction agreement, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 32)
    - Auburn/Opelika construction subcontract, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Auburn/Opelika design and construction billings, 1991-1993 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Auburn/Opelika correspondence, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Opelika meeting notes (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Calhoun County construction agreement (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Calhoun County billings and payments, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Calhoun County correspondence, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Calhoun County design agreement (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Calhoun County assignment of Borrower's Interest in Contract Documents (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Calhoun County promotional materials, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Dothan County billings and payments, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Dothan County agreements, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Greenville billings and payments, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Greenville correspondence, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Greenville agreements, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Huntsville billings and payments, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Huntsville correspondence, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Huntsville notes and drafts, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Huntsville agreements, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Deerwood Pointe correspondence, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Deerwood Pointe billings and payments, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Deerwood Pointe construction agreement, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Deerwood Pointe design agreement, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Domino's Farms development correspondence, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Domino's Farms development design agreement, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Ipswich deed and agreement (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Leonard and Morrison invoices, correspondence, 1997 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Legends limited partner meeting, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Golf development inc. documents, 1981, 1990-1996 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Golf developments lawsuit [RESTRICTED], 1990s (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Legends settlement documents [RESTRICTED] (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Golf developments FYE, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Raskas, Ruthmeyer, Pemerantz, Wynee, Garavaglia and Susman correspondence, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Alabama reimbursable design expenses, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Alabama invoices, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified drawings (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Florida Golf Corp. cash flow report, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Coral Ridge year end financial statement, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Oxmoor drafts (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Oxmoor design billings and payments, 1990-1991 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Oxmoor correspondence and memos, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Oxmoor construction meeting notes (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Oxmoor agreements, licensing application (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Oxmoor master plan, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Oxmoor miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Miller's Park drafts, 1990s (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Miller's Park billings and payments, 1990s (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Miller's Park contracts and agreements, 1990s (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Miller's Park background material, 1990s (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Miller's Park notes, evaluations, 1990s (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Miller's Park correspondence and memos, 1990s (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Manassas irrigation, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Aquamatic sprinkle system Inc., 1986-1990 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Horseshoe Bay, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Marrakesh, 1986-1990 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Manassas equipment sales, 1987-1990 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Liberty State Park, NJ, 1989-1990 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Old Warson Country Club, 1991-1992 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - La Gorce Country Club, 1993-1994 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Kananaskis, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 9, 10)
    - Japan (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Great Gorge Village (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Anglebrook Golf Club, 1993-1994 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Mauna Kea, 1989-1994 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Metedonk, 1985-1986 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Dunes Golf and Beach Club, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Manassas billings, 1988-1990 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Manassas, 1987-1991 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Manassas Virginia Project, 1988-1990 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Manassas builders notice corp, 1986-1989 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Calabasas Golf Course, Calabasas, CA - Specs, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - California Golf Club, San Mateo County, CA - Specs, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Cold Spring Country Club, Cold Spring, NY - Specs, 1960s (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - College of the Virgin Islands, St. Thomas, Virgin Islands - Specs (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Fountain Valley Golf Course, St. Croix, US Virgin Islands - Specs, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Golf de Bercuit, Belgium - Specs, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Hartford Golf Club, West Hartford, CT - Specs, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Hilldale Village Golf Course, Hoffman Estates, IL - Specs, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Lakewood Public Utility, Humphreys-Houston, TN - Specs, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Suntree Development Corporation Golf Course - Specs (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock Country Club, Woodstock, VT - Irrigation Specs (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Marbella plans (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Madeira plans (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Gujan-Mestras correspondence, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Specs- miscellaneous irrigation (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Specs- copies for new jobs (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - La Grande Motte correspondence (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Fax Recd., 1990 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Guadiaro plans (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Rome plans and reports (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - La Grande Motte green sketches, irrigation study, notes0 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Sperone Plans (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Sperone irrigation calculation sheets (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Sperone contracts, notes (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Day planners (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Day planners (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Joyenval plans (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Castel del Nero plans, project info (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Madeira (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Castel Gandolfo daily reports (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Sperone (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Vidauban funding, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Cyprus Limni Mines route plan development (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Fax Recd., 1990-1991 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Invoices, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Nimes, 1986-1987 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Rome, Castel Gandolfo (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Elba Rado invoices, general expenses and marbella expenses, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Valescure (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Conturbia landscape notes (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Sperone route plan evolution (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Moliets IV route plan evolution, irrigation notes (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Vilamoura, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Vidauban irrigation plans, cart path and maintenance road plan (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Grande Motte specs (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Booking forms, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Valderamma- daily reports (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Copies letters, 1985-1988 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Villa Moura plans (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Moilets Golf Course - Plans, 1987-1989 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Joyenval - Plans (1), 1986-1988 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Joyenval - Plans (2), 1986-1988 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Joyenval - Plans (3) (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Nominas - Payroll (1), 1989 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Nominas - Payroll (2), 1987-1988 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - La Grande Motte - Contracts and Invoices, 1985-1988 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Robert Trent Jones Anstalt - Design Contracts, 1985-1987 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Robert Trent Jones Anstalt - Construction Contracts, 1985-1987 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Mountain Golf Developments, Ltd. - Contracts, 1985-1987 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Amilroy Ltd., Inter Continental Golf Developments Ltd., Robert Trent Jones Limited and Linksland Golf Construction, 1985-1987 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Labor (Payroll) (1), 1989 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Labor (Payroll) (2), 1989 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Labor (Payroll) (3), 1989 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Dominican Republic - Plans (1), 1988 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Dominican Republic - Plans (2), 1988 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Pevero Golf Club, Sardegna (Italy) - Plans and Sketches, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Castel Del Nero, Italy - Plans, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Pevero Golf Club and Castel del Nero, Italy - Topographical Plans (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Jardin de Palmerie, Marrakech, Morocco - Reports, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Campo de Golf La Duques, Marbella, Malaga, 1986 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Campo de Golf La Duques, Marbella, Malaga, 1986-1987 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Madeira specs (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Accounts, all companies, 1987-1989 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Castogandolfo specs (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Rayburn Country Club correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Ridgewood Country Club, 1949-1961 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Atlanta athletic, 1966 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Riverbend, 1966-1967 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - American Golf Course Construction Co., 1966-1970 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Riverbend publicity (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Rochester Country Club, 1960 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Royal Kaanapali Golf Course, Maui, HI - Janns Corp., 1969-1970 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - American factors ltd., 1965 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Chamonix Golf Club - Specs (1), 1979-1980 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Chamonix Golf Club - Specs (2), 1979-1980 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Valescure - Contracts and Invoices, 1987-1989 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Valescure - Correspondence (1), 1988 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Valescure - Correspondence (2), 1988 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Castelgandolfo, Rome, Italy - Specs (1), 1985 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Castelgandolfo, Rome, Italy - Specs (2), 1985 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Castel Conturbia Golf Club, Italy - Specs, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Castel del Nero Golf Club, Italy, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Mt. Vesuvius Golf Club, Italy, 1981 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Falcon's Lair Golf Course, Mesquite, TX - Specs, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Grand Beach Golf Course, Galveston, TX - Nine Hole Executive Course Specs (Box 163, Folder 2)